vaporcouture.com 2016-11-03

# Privacy Policy | V2.com

Effective Date of Current Privacy Policy: June 7th 2010

### We Share Your Concerns About Safeguarding Personal Information

V2.com fully understands the need to protect your personal information while online and has developed this policy as a means to provide you with the utmost privacy possible. This Privacy Policy (referred to later as "Policy") describes our practices regarding the collection and use of information throughout our website, located at www.V2.com (referred to later as the "Site"). By using the Site or obtaining any product or service through this Site, you agree to the limited collection and use of information as outlined in this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use the Site.

We may from time to time update this Policy to reflect changing technology and other factors. We will notify you of changes to the Policy by posting the updated Policy on this page. We ask that you bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure that you remain familiar with the most current version of the Policy. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by checking the "Effective Date of Current Policy" legend at the top of the Policy.

### V2.com collects two basic types of information during your visits to our Site.

First, we collect non-personally identifiable information. This is general information that cannot be traced to individuals and contains no personalized data, think of it as a simple census form. When visitors come to our Site, we collect and aggregate information indicating, among other things, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which links on the site were clicked by visitors. Collecting such information involves logging the IP addresses, operating system and browser software used by each visitor to the Site. Although such information is not personally identifiable, it may be possible to determine from an IP address a visitor’s Internet Service Provider and the general geographic location of the visitor’s point of connectivity. We then use this information in making modifications and improvements to the site to provide you the user with both a smoother and more efficient shopping experience.

We also use non-invasive "cookies" and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information which we then use to provide you with an easier shopping experience. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser. These cookies do not track other websites you might visit and they do not plant malware on your computer. Our non-invasive cookies simply make it possible for us to recognize your browser once you visit our Site. By doing this, we can personalize your return visits and save you time during checkout. Your browser must be set to accept cookies in order for you to enjoy the benefits of being a registered user of the Site. If you are uncomfortable with the cookies on your computer, you can always remove them by accessing the options menu of your browser. Please refer to your browser’s help menu for more specific directions if needed.

Second, we collect personally identifiable information as needed to provide you with requested services and to process any order you might place. In general, our Site uses an order form; a registration form and a newsletter request form so that you can request information, products and services from us. These forms require that you provide us with personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, and credit card number, to receive the requested service.

Further, when you use the Site to purchase a product or service as a gift, we will collect from you personally identifiable information regarding the gift recipient or potential gift recipient so that we can deliver the gift to them if requested.

Please take some time to familiarize yourself with the different ways that V2.com uses the information that we gather. Keep in mind that, while we encourage all third parties involved in running our business to adhere to our policies regarding the privacy of our visitors and to handle personally identifiable information in a responsible manner, we cannot and do not assume any responsibility for any actions or omissions of third parties, including the manner in which they use information received either from V2.com or independently.

### Non-personally identifiable information

V2.com uses non-personally identifiable information, such as your IP address and the pages that you visit on our Site, to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our Site and improve Site-related services and features. Your IP address and other non-personally identifiable information also may be used to gather broad demographic information and to recognize customer traffic patterns and Site usage trends. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design and layout of the Site.

We use Google Analytics on our websites, across multiple platforms and different devices. The information gathered assists VMR to compile reports on web activity, internet usage, and to improve our websites. If you do not want your data reported by Google Analytics, you may opt-out by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. This add-on instructs the Google Analytics JavaScript not to send your visit information to Google Analytics. Please note that the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on does not prevent information from being sent to the website itself. Learn more about the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on [here](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881?hl=en).

We also might share aggregated statistical data and other non-personally identifiable information with our current and potential business partners, and with our service providers to help them provide similar services.

### Personally identifiable information

V2.com uses personally identifiable information collected from you to complete transactions initiated by you, particularly the sale and delivery of products and services. Your personally identifiable information is also used to get in touch with you when necessary regarding questions about any order you might place. We may also use personally identifiable information to contact you to make sure you are satisfied with our goods and services or to find out how we can serve you better. Your decision to participate in any survey or questionnaire about this is completely voluntary. Further, we may use personally identifiable information to conduct in-depth marketing research regarding our customers and potential customers.

Financial information (credit card numbers, credit card expiration dates, billing address, and so forth) is used solely to bill you for products and services and we make every effort to keep your information secure from theft or fraud. We use industry standard encryption technologies, and all credit card / bank information submitted on this web-site is transmitted directly to our merchant bank and never stored locally on the v2.com servers. As a further precaution, V2 staff has no access to your financial information, only the owners of the company and a small handful of senior managers have access to our merchant processing interface.

You may, from time to time, receive information from us regarding new features, new products and services and special offers we think you'll find valuable. If you'd like to opt out of receiving future mailings from V2.com, please [Click Here](https://www.v2.com/help/contact) and contact us.

V2.com also may use your personally identifiable information to "pre-populate" forms that are used by the Site to facilitate transactions with us and save you from entering every data field on the checkout.

Special instances when we might use personally identifiable information are discussed below.

### Gift Recipients

As noted above, we collect personally identifiable information regarding gift recipients and people to whom you may wish to give gifts in the future. This is done in order to accommodate proper gift delivery to such recipients and remind you of upcoming gift-giving occasions. We do not sell or rent any personally identifiable information that you provide to us about such persons, but gift recipients may, from time to time, receive offers from us via postal mailings regarding new features, new products and services and special offers we think they will find of interest. Also we may send marketing offers via postal mailings to gift recipients on behalf of ourselves and our subsidiaries. In connection with such offers, we allow gift recipients to opt out of receiving future marketing-related postal mailings from us.

### Service Providers

We work with third parties who provide services, including but not limited to website hosting, order processing and fulfillment, credit card clearance, e-commerce affiliation, data analysis, emailing and other services of an administrative nature. Personally identifiable information, including financial information, is shared with such third parties for the purpose of providing such services and is limited to the intended purpose only.

Further, we may use selected reputable third parties for marketing, targeting and analysis purposes. Some of these third parties may be given access to some, or all, of the information that you provide to us and may use cookies or other tracking technologies in connection with providing their services. To the extent that we provide your personally identifiable information to such third parties, we restrict their ability to use such information for their own marketing purposes to the best of our abilities; however, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies or practices of such third parties.

We do not disclose an individual customer's personally identifiable information to third parties for any third-party direct marketing purposes. If you have been contacted by a third party, other than V2 or one of its subsidiaries, who is privy to information you provided us, please contact our customer service department immediately and we will do everything in our power to investigate the issue. In addition, we also allow you to decide whether you want to receive further marketing information from us. If you do not want V2.com to send you announcements or special offers by email, please [Click Here](https://www.v2.com/help/contact) and inform us of such.

V2.com sometimes administers online surveys in connection with the Site in which we ask you for demographic information and opinions. We do not ask you for personally identifiable information as part of a survey. We use the collected survey data on an aggregated basis to better understand the needs of all of our customers.

V2.com may send to you periodic announcements regarding status updates, service changes concerning the Site and other administrative matters.

Subject to applicable law, we reserve the right to release information concerning any Site visitor where such visitor is believed to be in violation of his or her obligations to us, is partaking (or is suspected of partaking) in any illegal activity, in response to civil subpoenas and discovery requests, to protect the interests of V2.com, our customers or others, and as otherwise permitted or required by law as regards to these special cases.

Emails from V2.com or its business partners, and the Site itself, may contain links to other Internet websites, including sites that may or may not be owned or operated by V2.com. Unless otherwise explicitly stated, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when email recipients or Site visitors click through links to those sites. If you visit such websites, we encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of the sites to ensure a safe browsing experience.

V2.com seeks to use reasonable security measures to help protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of personally identifiable information that is under our control. Unfortunately, no security system, or system of transmitting data over the Internet, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result of the foregoing, while we seek to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of our servers, the means by which information is transmitted between your computer and V2.com’s servers, or any information provided to us or to any third party through or in connection with the Site. You provide all such information at your own risk, but please remember that these risks can be minimized by using responsible browsing habits such as the use of anti-virus software and similar protection measures.

If you have signed up for an account with V2.com, you may update your mailing address, email address, name changes or telephone number by visiting the homepage and clicking "My Account" located at the top of the page. After signing in, you can access this personal information by clicking "your account details" located in the menu options at the center of the page. This takes you to a page with all of the account information we store locally about you. Please take the time to make sure your information is accurate for timely delivery as well as keeping your mailing preferences updated.

If you have any questions about this Policy, the data collection and usage practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, or if you wish to report a violation of this Policy, you can mail us at:

Customer Service  
V2.com

1521 Alton Road Suite 275  
Miami Beach, FL 33139-3301

OR by clicking the link below

V2.com is committed to quality customer experience. We constantly review your feedback to find ways to improve and enhance your shopping experience. You can tell us what you think by sending us an email or contacting our customer care department toll-free at 1-877-37-VAPOR (82767).
